screensaversplanet.com 2019-12-07

# Terms of use - Screensavers Planet

We care deeply about the privacy and safety of those who, like you, visit this website, and we aim to make our services as transparent as possible. To that effect, we have set up the privacy policy and terms of service outlined below, informing you of the data we collect during your visit and the terms which govern your use of this website.

Please note that by accessing this website, you accept the terms set forth below and that this policy may be changed at any time without prior notice.

This page was last updated on April 26, 2018.

## Privacy policy

### Logging of anonymous usage data

When you access any part of our website, we will inevitably learn certain information about you. Most of that information, such as the time of visit and the type of internet browser used, is not personally identifiable. This data is automatically written to log files, later to be analyzed in aggregate so that we can improve our services.

Some examples of such data, provided to us by your web browser, include: time and date of visit, the referring website, your computer's operating system, the pages you access and how quickly they load, keywords used to search, and your IP address.

We collect this information for internal use only, and will never share, sell or otherwise expose any part of these log files without your explicit consent.

### Analytics

To further improve our understanding of users' interaction with the content on this website, we currently employ Google Analytics, a service that collects anonymous data from each user — similar to our own logging (above) but using cookies — and then combines that data into useful reports. Google Analytics does not store any personal information about our users. For more details, please refer to the [Google Analytics privacy policy](https://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html).

### Advertising and cookies

This website is entirely ad-supported. In order to display the most contextually relevant advertising, we have teamed up with Google AdSense, a program that connects web publishers to advertisers. When you view or click on an ad, a cookie may be stored on your computer. Cookies are small text files that are commonly used on the web to store user preferences, and to recognize returning visitors, so that their experience can be optimized.

Third party vendors and advertising networks, including Google, use these cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to this website. Google's use of the so-called "DoubleClick" cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to this site and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising, as well as other cookies, by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

Please see [this page](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/partner-sites/) for an overview of how Google uses information from this website.

### Information voluntarily provided

Sometimes it may be necessary to provide us with personally identifiable information, such as your name and e-mail address, so that we can assist you with a query, for example. Whenever you send us an e-mail, or contact us in other ways, we make sure that your information is kept safe and private, and that it is stored no longer than necessary.

## Disclaimer

Screensavers Planet is a free service, provided on an as is and as available basis. We make no guarantees regarding the availability and/or functionality of the service, and while we put a lot of effort into creating and maintaining a usable and safe environment, we accept no responsibility for any damages caused by your use of the service, whether directly or indirectly. We regularly scan and test every download and link made available through this service, but this is no substitute for taking your own security precautions.

This website is owned and operated by Mindcircus Media in The Netherlands.

If you have any questions or comments, please do not hesitate to contact us.
